My dear Spider,
what would you say is the most
human thing a person can do is?
It's when they leave behind a dying message.
Envisioning the world after their death...
Putting their thoughts into words...
Of all creatures, those are skills exclusive to mankind.
Wow, that's one heck of a skyline.
They don't call Mitario Mouzaia's
largest metropolis for nothing.
Spider, are you listening to me?
You're a lucky guy, Purple Ant,
getting to work out of a city this-
What the hell, man?!
It's your own fault for not paying attention.
You deserve to die thrice over for that.
But your monologues are always so long.
Well, whatever.
I've got a mission for you.
Starting next month,
the Tolfa Economic Conference is gonna be running
here in the Westport Building for half a year.
It's got a big, fancy name,
but it's a glorified squabble over rights.
The whole continent of Tolfa's been
a mess since the war,
and the Allies want to figure out
how they're gonna carve up the pie.
How revolting.
Spies from all across the world are gonna be there.
The Fend Commonwealth's CIM will be
sending in the entire Retias team.
Smart money says the Bumal Kingdom will send in
Shadowseed and the Goosefoot Sisters.
Mouzaia's intelligence agency, the JJJ,
will have their cream of the crop there too.
You'll need to watch out for the Giraffe and the Turtle.
Plus, with how big an event it is, there's no way
that mysterious spy Ouka doesn't show up as well.
We're talking an international all-star roster.
Your job is to kill them all.
That's a little grisly, don't you think?
I'm counting on you.
Sooner or later, all of them
would have gotten in our way.
Oh, and there's one other guy who'll probably come.
The rising star from the Din Republic's
Foreign Intelligence Office:
Bonfire.
Don't you worry about me.
Here in Mitario, I reign as king.
To think that it's already been
a month since that conversation.
Oh, how the time flies.
Can I offer you a drink, my fair lady?
You're a spy from the Din Republic, yes?
I must say, I was expecting you to be older.
Might I ask for your name?
Well, no matter.
I'll guess it before long.
Until then, let's chat, you and I.
We can share the tale of how you
and yours took me on
and were met with brutal defeat.
Me wo aketa kikkake wa
Kokoro saku joukei
Hirari hirari yubi no sukima kara
Mietekuru shinjitsu wo nirame
Kizukareta no wa, rakuen?
Massakasama ochite
Aa tatoe kouya demo
Hitori de ikiru to oritachimashou
Ikanakucha
Koko ni aru hana wa ima eien nare to
Gokujou no chihedo wo haite watashi ga ueta mono
Kono koe de ashi de te de watashi no mama mogaku hodo ni
Doushiyou mo nai sekai ga itoshii
Tadoritsuku wa kanarazu
Musekaeru hodo no yume
MISSION: Dreamspeaker I
This mission is going to involve
infiltrating a foreign country.
Serpent is hiding in the United States of Mouzaia,
over in the New World.
This is going to be a major trial for all of you.
Thea, you're going to be in charge of
command and control at the mission site.
Grete will be in charge of planning.
Keep the situation in mind
and give effective orders to the team.
W-wait, hold on.
What about you, Teach?
You've grown enough to help lighten my load.
That'll allow me to operate more freely and
from a position that makes better use of my skills.
I'm going to be standing on the front lines.
The Cabinet Office Economic Research Center?
This is one of the buildings
the Foreign Intelligence Office uses.
There's something I want to show you.
Simply put, this is a prison.
It's where the Foreign Intelligence Office houses
the majority of the spies it captures.
Hey there, Bonfire.
Just the guy I was hoping to see.
If they sent in another weakling,
I might've just killed them again.
Corpse...
Or, I guess they call you Deepwater
over in the Empire.
Roland is fine.
It's what I'm used to.
Hey, Bonfire, how about we have us
a fight to the death, one-on-one?
You won't catch me by surprise this time.
I don't have time to play around.
Bummer.
In that case, I guess I'll have to take that girl
and kill her.
You've already lost.
Your only job is to cough up intel.
The Empire's elite team Serpent has infiltrated
the United States' city of Mitario
and is interfering with the Tolfa Economic Conference.
Do I have that right?
Yeah, I was helping Purple Ant out.
Purple Ant...
That's the Serpent member they have there?
Where is he, exactly?
What does he look like?
Let me out of here, and I'll tell you.
If you try to go in blind,
Purple Ant will slaughter you all.
Just like last time,
you'll lose those precious teammates of yours.
Spare me the empty threats.
You should kick the dark-haired kid off your team.
Back when we fought, she was useless.
All she did was shake in her boots and flee.
You'd be better off cutting her loose
before she drags you down.
You know, I actually had something
I wanted to ask you.
Why did you think that you and I could be rivals?
You're just a two-bit nothing.
Know your place.
Your life as a spy is over.
I'm sorry about that.
You're going to be the one giving
the orders during this mission,
so I thought it would be good for you
to see where our intel was coming from.
Don't apologize.
Everything Roland said was true.
All I did back then was tremble.
And on top of that...
Thea, honey, you're a nobody.
You're soft, and it made manipulating you
so incredibly effortless.
Teach, I-
Wasn't that last right the turn to get to the station?
I-I'm so sorry.
The car just started acting up.
I can't make it drop below sixty kilometers an hour.
Pardon me.
This is no standard malfunction.
Has anything odd happened to you lately?
There was this bearded man who told me
that he knew what I'd done.
What did you do?
I stole some money from the safe at my job.
He told me that if I wanted him to keep quiet,
that I had to give you two a ride in my taxi.
I see.
You sort of brought this on yourself,
but we should at least compensate you
for getting you involved.
Once this is over, call this number.
Wh-who are you people?
Don't worry about it.
Now, close your eyes and cover your ears.
Teach, what's going on?
You've gotten good at masking your presence,
Annette.
I take it this is your doing?
Aw, I've been found!
Annette?!
I've got a message for you from Lily.
If you want the taxi to stop, just admit that you lose.
We've got a big mission coming up,
so we're coming at you with everything we've got!
It's time for you to get a taste of how much
we've grown on our domestic missions!
Magnificent.
And on that note, I'm out, yo!
But, Annette, what about me?
You're a hostage, Sis.
Try to slow Klaus down for us.
Wh-
And a hip, hop, and away we go!
T-Teach, you have to stop the car!
You can do it, right?!
I could, but this is Annette we're talking about.
She probably has the taxi rigged
to explode as soon as it stops.
I want to get off this wild ride!
For now, we need to get out of the city.
I'll stop the car somewhere out of
their homing device's reception.
The question is, why only sixty kilometers an hour?
At this speed, I can still turn.
Surely they could have set it a bit faster.
E-easy enough for you to say...
It's the bird.
The homing device never mattered.
They have Aiden tracking us.
Ah, I get it.
And sixty kilometers an hour is slow enough
for a pigeon to keep up.
You're not going anywhere.
How unlucky.
Hope you're ready!
No remorse about friendly fire, huh?
Yeah, I figured I didn't stand
much of a chance against you.
But hey, guess what I just nicked?
Go show him why you're our ace!
Don't mind if I do.
Too slow by half.
No way...
We can't beat him, even with
three people attacking in waves?
No worries.
We've got four.
You're wide open, Klaus.
It's over.
W-we did it?
We finally beat Teach?
MISSION: Dreamspeaker I
Ah, I see.
The first Monika who showed up
was Grete in disguise.
That's right.
Just as I expected.
Even you would have no choice
but to give Monika your full attention, Boss.
I had hoped that might leave you vulnerable.
Come on, Klaus.
Let's hear that surrender.
Magnificent.
You've grown so strong.
I knew you all had boundless talents
just waiting to be set free.
As I recall, you're still only on
your provisional academy graduations.
You each still have plenty of problem areas,
but the explosive power you've shown working
together as a team is on par with that of full graduates.
We'll call this next mission your graduation exam.
On par with full graduates?
I never thought I would hear him say it.
Oh, and also,
how much longer should I keep
playing along with this game?
The cops?
But I told the driver what'd happen
if she told a soul, yo.
That woman was so loose-lipped,
I was able to blackmail her, too.
I told her that I would help cover up her embezzlement
as long as she called the cops for me.
That note...
If I were you, I would get out while the getting is good.
How do you think the police are going to feel
about the way you're holding a fine,
upstanding citizen at gunpoint?
L-let's book it!
Retreat!
Agreed!
Quit dawdlin', let's go!
Wh-who, me?
C'mon, hurry up!
We need to move!
Wait, how many people have we got
riding in this damn thing?!
Aww, what a bummer.
And we were so close, too.
You know, we might have actually won
if we'd included Thea in the plan.
Huh?
If you'd been in charge of getting
the driver on our side,
the negotiation probably
would have gone a lot cleaner.
Leaving me in the dark was the right call.
If I'd known what was going to happen,
Teach would have seen right through me.
Really? I dunno about that.
It's true.
They didn't need me.
I gotta say, I'm pretty excited
about visiting the United States.
I wonder if we'll get a chance to go sightseeing
after the mission's over?
I wanna check out one of those baseball games
they keep talkin' about.
I want to watch a TV broadcast, yo.
I'm gonna buy up every appliance I find!
I might go check out some museums and galleries.
I want to go see the big famous goddess statue!
I want to buy a bunch of records as souvenirs.
I love jazz.
I would love to visit a music hall with the boss.
What about you, Thea?
What're you looking forward to?
Me? I-I haven't given it much thought.
United States, here we come!
Are you sure we'll be fine with me in charge?
I'm too kind to my enemies.
I'm not fit to lead.
I really think that you should be
the one giving the orders.
I'm afraid I can't agree.
But why not?!
There's too much we don't know about our opponent.
With how little intel we have,
I need to be the one standing on the front lines
and shouldering that danger.
There it is! Mouzaia!
Is that really Mitario?
What a gigantic city.
Don't be so down on yourself.
Like I said before, differences between allies
are the key to a strong team.
There times when what the team
needs is ruthlessness,
but there are times when that kindness
of yours is what it needs, too.
Do you really believe that?
I do.
Well, I'll do what I can.
Right now, the United States of Mouzaia
sits at the heart of the world economy.
Instead of participating in the Great War directly,
they merely supplied weapons and food to the Allies,
allowing them to flourish unimpeded.
The economic conference isn't the
only thing going on in Mitario.
Between the B2B meetings,
political fundraising parties,
and military discussions held behind closed doors,
there are over a thousand gatherings
of various sizes taking place.
It's no wonder the conference
takes place over such a long time.
That jazz band often gets hired to play
at politicians' parties and social gatherings.
It's the perfect infiltration point for gathering intel from.
She's a natural pro.
She really is.
Minister!
Minster, what are your thoughts heading into
this meeting with the Lylat Kingdom?
I have questions about the way you've been
appeasing the Galgad Empire.
C'mon, old man.
At least answer our damn questions, will ya?
Wh-why, I never!
What nation do you report for?
I'm with the Din Republic's Randium Times.
What about it?
Well, you're in the way.
Move it!
Sybilla is using her position as a newspaper journalist
to interact with politicians and bureaucrats
from around the world.
Dang, he gave me the slip.
I nicked the minister's business card case.
Hope it's useful.
She's as skillful as ever.
She really is.
Thanks for waiting!
Here's your cheeseburger combo meals!
Um, not to be a bother, but...
What's up?
Did you have a question for me?
That is to say,
a question for the exchange student attending
the Mitario University School of Pharmacy?
A question for Lillian Hepburn, the eighteen-year-old
who got this job to pay her way?
Thank you for saving me the trouble
of explaining your backstory.
Hey, Lillian, take this up to
Conference Room 13 on the fourth floor.
Sure!
The primary Tolfa Economic Conference meetings
are taking place on the upper floors of this building.
Well, it looks like she's doing a good job blending in.
She is, but...
These are fish burgers, not cheeseburgers.
I just hope she doesn't end up getting fired.
Toodles!
Finally, we have the Specialist squad trio.
Question 100...
This is last one, okay?
The Westport Building is forty-eight stories tall.
On the eighth floor, there's a rooftop garden.
Please list every point you could snipe a target
sitting on the garden's north-side bench from.
There's five of them.
Lyment Hall...
Nywengate Tower...
The construction site next door would work.
And with a top-of-the-line sniper rifle,
you could make the shot from Mitario Hotel
or the art hall's control room.
Good work!
You got the correct-
I found another one, yo.
There's a circus staying at
West Kopek Plaza next week.
You could hit the target from on top of the tent.
There's no way.
That wouldn't be tall enough to reach the garden.
But if the target was on the north bench,
you could still hit them.
What kind of sniper goes and
climbs on top of a circus tent?!
We can't let ourselves get bogged down
by common sense, yo.
Y-yeep?!
You're both right, and you both get full points.
Good work.
We brought you something, if you'd like.
You were watching that,
Miss Thea and Miss Grete?
Just for a bit.
The two of them are so talented.
The questions were pretty hard,
and they got them all correct.
To be honest, they're both
a lot better at all this than I am.
Not at all.
If anything, the way you're able to rein them in
is the most impressive skill of all.
Let's review the full situation.
What are all the other nations' spies up to?
So, about that.
The boss already got ahold of some intel.
Apparently, spies are being
snuffed out one after another.
What do we do?
We'll need to keep in close touch with the others.
That way, we'll be able to quickly
dispatch backup if they get in trouble.
Even so, though, there's only
so much we'll be able to do.
We'll have to trust in their ability to
handle things on their own.
G-good point.
We should pass along that intel
and tell them to be on guard.
You can go ahead and leave that to me.
Okay.
I'll get on that, then.
I'm the only one in a slump.
Everyone else is firing on all cylinders.
They're all motivated, and none of them
have their hearts plagued by doubt.
I'm being left behind all on my own.
What kind of spy am I trying to become?
I don't want you to be just any old spy.
I want you to become a hero.
Spies can only save their own people.
But heroes, heroes can save so much more.
The way I am now,
I can't even save my own teammates.
They could end up dead, and it would all be my fault.
I finished making breakfast, Thea.
Looks delicious.
Still, we're bringing it all the way over?
That's right.
Good morning.
Sorry for asking you to do this.
Good morning!
Four plates, huh?
Yes...
I felt I didn't have much choice.
There's no need for you to go out of your way like that.
Starting tomorrow, I'll handle the cooking myself.
Ooh, something smells good.
Is it time for breakfast?
Perfect timing.
I'm famished.
Aa, kataashi de tatte tsurai okimochi
Mou kyouyuu shite chanto yottemasuka?
Ai o motte chigau nanika abiserare
Yakkaisou de jama na watashi, waita waita
Honto daijoubu?
Sore kiite dou suru no?
Tada homeru dake de ii
Iienai ienai kagami no sei
Mirenai kienai yogoreta sei
Assari kamikitte sameta me de uso o minuku
Katenai kaenai na muku na hin
Suteru mono nai mukurodashi
Kakugo wa kakusazu hada de te ni motte aragau
(whoo, whoo, ooh)
Rakugaki darake no aimai na unmei
Kami de sae keisotsu ni damashiteku